younkers.com 2019-09-12

# Privacy Policy - Younkers

| 

###### Effective as of 3/15/2019

This “Privacy Policy” describes the privacy practices of The Bon-Ton Holdings, Inc. and our subsidiaries and affiliates (collectively, “Bon-Ton”, “we”, “us”, or “our”) in connection with the www.bonton.com website, and any other website that we own or control and which posts or links to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the “Websites”).

Bon-Ton is a member of the CSC Generation group of companies. CSC is a multi-brand technology platform that uses proprietary technology and centralized teams to create and foster e-commerce companies.

Bon-Ton may provide additional or supplemental privacy policies for specific products, services, and promotions. These supplemental privacy policies will govern how we may process the information in the context of the specific product, service, or promotion.

### Personal information we collect

#### Information you give us

Personal information you may provide through the Websites or otherwise communicate to us includes:

  * Contact information, such as first and last name, email and mailing addresses, phone or fax number, of you, or the billing or shipping contact
  * Content you choose to provide via the Websites, such as text, images, audio, and video, along with the metadata associated with the files you upload
  * Profile information, such as your interests, preferences, wish list, and other information you provide to us
  * Feedback or correspondence, such as information you provide when you contact us with questions, feedback, or otherwise correspond with us online
  * Demographic Information, such as your city, state, country of residence, postal code, and age
  * Payment information, such as details regarding your payment card or other method of payment
  * Transaction information, such as details of products or services you have purchased from us
  * Usage information, such as information about how you use the Websites and interact with us, including products you view
  * Marketing information, such as information such your preferences for receiving communications about our activities, events, and publications, and details about how you engage with our communications

### Information we obtain from third-party platforms and social media networks

We may maintain pages for our company, and our products and services on third-party platforms, such as Facebook, LinkedIn, Twitter, Google+, YouTube, Instagram, and other social networking services. When you interact with our pages on those third-party platforms, the third-party’s privacy policy will govern your interactions on the relevant platform. You may choose to provide us with information through the third-party platform, and we will treat such information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. If the third party platform provides us with information about our pages on those platforms or your interactions with them, we will also treat that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

### Information we obtain from other third parties

We may receive personal information about you from third-party sources, such as our business or marketing partners. We may combine this information with information that we have collected from you or other sources.

### Cookies and other information collected by automated means

We, our service providers, and our business partners may automatically log information about you, your computer or mobile device, and activity occurring on or through the Websites. The information that may be collected automatically includes your computer or mobile device operating system type and version number, manufacturer and model, device identifier, browser type, screen resolution, IP address, the website you visited before browsing to our website, general location information such as city, state or geographic area; and information about your use of and actions on the Websites, such as pages you viewed, how long you spent on a page, navigation paths between pages, information about your activity on a page, access times, and length of access. Our service providers and business partners may collect this type of information over time and across third-party websites and mobile applications. This information is collected using cookies, browser web storage, Flash LSOs, web beacons, and similar technologies, and our emails may also contain web beacons.

A “cookie” is a text file that websites send to a visitor‘s computer or other Internet-connected device to uniquely identify the visitor’s browser or to store information or settings in the browser. “Browser web storage,” also known as locally stored objects (“LSOs”), is used for similar purposes as cookies. Browser web storage enables the storage of a larger amount of data than cookies. A “web beacon,” also known as a pixel tag or clear GIF, is typically used to demonstrate that a webpage was accessed or that certain content was viewed, typically to measure the success of our marketing campaigns or engagement with our emails and to compile statistics about usage of our websites.

Web browsers may offer users of our websites the ability to disable receiving certain types of cookies; however, if cookies are disabled, some features or functionality of our websites may not function correctly. Please see the “Targeted online advertising” section for information about how to exercise choice regarding the use of browsing behavior for purposes of targeted advertising.

### Referrals

Website users may have the opportunity to refer friends or other contacts to us. If you are an existing user, you may only submit a referral if you have permission to provide the referral’s contact information to us.

### How we use your personal information

We use personal information for the following purposes and as otherwise described in this Privacy Policy or at the time of collection. 

We use personal information to:

  * provide, operate and improve the Websites
  * process and fulfill your purchases
  * establish and maintain your user profile
  * enable security features, such as sending you security codes via email or SMS, and remembering devices from which you have previously logged in
  * communicate with you, including by sending you announcements, updates, security alerts, and support and administrative messages
  * operate our rewards program
  * send you marketing or promotional communications
  * communicate with you about events, contests, and promotions in which you participate
  * understand your needs and interests, and personalize your experience and our communications
  * improve and analyze use of the Websites and develop new products and services
  * provide support and maintenance
  * to respond to your requests, questions and feedback

In addition, we may use your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to: (a) comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; (b) protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); (c) enforce the terms and conditions; and (d) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity.

We may also create de-identified data from your personal information and other individuals whose personal information we collect by removing information that makes the data personally identifiable to you. We may use this de-identified data and share it with third parties for our lawful business purposes, including analyzing and improving the Websites and promoting our business.

### How we share your personal information

#### Affiliates

We may share your personal information with current or future members of the CSC Generation group of companies, including our corporate parent, subsidiary, and affiliate companies.

#### Service providers

We may share your personal information with third party companies and individuals that provide services on our behalf or help us operate the Websites (such as customer support, order fulfillment, hosting, analytics, email delivery, marketing, and database management services). These third parties may use your personal information only as directed or authorized by us and in a manner consistent with this Privacy Policy, and are prohibited from using or disclosing your information for any other purpose.

#### Business and strategic partners

We may sometimes share your personal information with business and strategic partners. These may include partners that run a joint promotion with us or other partners whose products or services we think may be of interest to you. If you receive marketing emails from these partners, you may opt out of such communications by following the instructions provided in the email.

#### Other Website users and the public

We may provide functionality that enables you to make public certain content that you post, such as product reviews. We may display your user name, first name and last name initial along with your city and state in connection with your review. We do not control how other users or third parties use any information that is publicly available on our Websites.

#### Professional advisors

We may disclose your personal information to professional advisors, such as lawyers, bankers, auditors and insurers, where necessary in the course of the professional services that they render to us.

#### For compliance, fraud prevention and safety

We may share your personal information as we believe necessary or appropriate to: (a) comply with applicable laws, lawful requests, and legal process, such as to respond to subpoenas or requests from government authorities; (b) protect our, your or others’ rights, privacy, safety or property (including by making and defending legal claims); (c) enforce the terms and conditions that govern the Websites; and (d) protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized, unethical or illegal activity.

#### Business transfers

We may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of our business or assets, including your personal information, in connection with a business transaction (or potential business transaction) such as a corporate divestiture, merger, consolidation, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, or in the event of bankruptcy or dissolution. In such a case, we will make reasonable efforts to require the recipient to honor this Privacy Policy.

### Your choices

#### Access or update your information

If you have registered for an account with us, you may review and update certain personal information in your account profile after logging into your account.

#### Opt out of marketing communications

You may opt out of marketing-related emails by following the opt-out or unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of the email. You may continue to receive service-related and other non-marketing emails. If you receive marketing text messages from us, you may opt out of receiving further marketing text messages from us by replying STOP to our marketing message.

#### Cookies & browser web storage

We may allow service providers and other third parties to use cookies and similar technologies to track your browsing activity over time and across the Websites and third party websites. Most browsers let you remove or reject cookies. To do this, follow the instructions in your browser settings. Many browsers accept cookies by default until you change your settings. Please note that if you set your browser to disable cookies, the Sites may not work properly. Similarly, your browser settings may allow you to clear your browser web storage.

#### Targeted online advertising

Some of the business partners that collect information about users’ activities on or through the Websites may be members of organizations or programs that provide choices to individuals regarding the use of their browsing behavior for purposes of targeted advertising.

Users may opt out of receiving targeted advertising on websites through members of the Network Advertising Initiative by clicking here or the Digital Advertising Alliance by clicking here. Please note that we also may work with companies that offer their own opt-out mechanisms and may not participate in the opt-out mechanisms that we linked above.

If you choose to opt-out of targeted advertisements, you will still see advertisements online but they may not be relevant to you. Even if you do choose to opt out, not all companies that serve online behavioral advertising are included in this list, so you may still receive some cookies and tailored advertisements from companies that are not listed.

#### Do Not Track

Some Internet browsers may be configured to send “Do Not Track” signals to the online services that you visit. We currently do not respond to “Do Not Track” or similar signals. To find out more about “Do Not Track,” please visit http://www.allaboutdnt.com.

#### Other sites, mobile applications and services

Our Websites may contain links to other websites, mobile applications, and online services operated by third parties. These links are not an endorsement of, or representation that we are affiliated with, any third party. In addition, our content may be included on web pages or in mobile applications or online services that are not associated with us. We do not control third party websites, mobile applications, or online services, and we are not responsible for their actions. Other websites and services follow different rules regarding the collection, use and sharing of your personal information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the other websites you visit and mobile applications and online services you use.

#### Security practices

The security of your personal information is important to us. We employ a number of organizational, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information we collect. However, security risk is inherent in all internet and information technologies and we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information.

#### Children

The Websites are not directed to, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from, anyone under the age of 13. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us. We will delete such information from our files as soon as reasonably practicable.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you by updating the date of this Privacy Policy and posting it on our website.

Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon our posting the new terms and/or upon implementation of the new changes on the Websites (or as otherwise indicated at the time of posting). In all cases, your continued use of the Websites after the posting of any modified Privacy Policy indicates your acceptance of the terms of the modified Privacy Policy.

How to contact us Please direct any questions or comments about this Policy or privacy practices to info@bonton.com. You may also write to us via postal mail at:

The Bon-Ton Holdings, Inc.  
Attn: Legal – Privacy  
8450 Broadway, Merrillville, IN 46410

### Your California Privacy Rights

Under California Civil Code section 1798.83, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information which we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to us via email at info@bonton.com or The Bon-Ton Holdings, Inc., Attn: Legal – Privacy / California Privacy Rights, 8450 Broadway, Merrillville, IN 46410. You must put the statement "Your California Privacy Rights" in your request and include your name, street address, city, state, and ZIP code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.  
  
---|---
